Guide to the Kentucky Foundation for Women Records, 1985-2017 RL.00773
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Grant Files Series, 1985-1993
  - 1986-1987
    - Churn, Hartina (Box GF 1)
    - Connerton, Martha (Box GF 1)
    - Dalton, Marcia (Box GF 1)
    - Eastley, Keely (Box GF 1)
    - Ewald, Wendy (Box GF 1)
    - Ferguson, Kathleen (Box GF 1)
    - Gifted Girls Conference (Box GF 1)
    - Glover, Sally (Box GF 1)
    - Griffin, Carol (Box GF 1)
    - Hazelwood, Kimberly (Box GF 1)
    - Kennedy, Margaret (Box GF 1)
    - Kentucky Center Chamber Players (Box GF 1)
    - Kentucky Contemporary Theater (Box GF 1)
    - Kilkelly, Ann (Box GF 1)
    - Kinchlow, Gina (Box GF 1)
    - Lundstrom, Kinda (Box GF 1)
    - Lyon, George Ella (Box GF 1)
    - Mims, Marilyn (Box GF 1)
    - Museum of History (Box GF 1)
    - Olmstead, Jane (Box GF 1)
    - Osbey, Brenda Marie (Box GF 1)
    - Naslund, Sena (Box GF 1)
    - Portland Museum (Box GF 1)
    - Presness, Barbara (Box GF 1)
    - Roadside Theater (Box GF 1)
    - Rodriguez, Andrea (Box GF 1)
    - Sutton, Catherine (Box GF 1)
    - Sutton, Dorothy (Box GF 1)
    - Theater Workshop of Louisville (Box GF 2)
    - Thorne, Florence (Box GF 2)
    - Troutman, Kira (Box GF 2)
    - University of Cincinnati, Sculpture Conference (Box GF 2)
    - Walker, Concetta (Box GF 2)
    - Ward, Lucretia (Box GF 2)
    - Women in Theater (Box GF 2)
    - Women Writers Conference (Box GF 2)
  - 1987 Fall: Grants review papers (Box GF 2)
  - 1987-1988 (Spring)
    - Anderson, Ann Stewart (Box GF 2)
    - Bach, Peggy (Box GF 2)
    - Banks, Barbara (Box GF 2)
    - Biggs, Karen (Box GF 2)
    - Blee, Kathleen (Box GF 2)
    - Bradshaw, Cathryn (Box GF 2)
    - Bunch, Marilyn (Box GF 2)
    - Butler, Linda (Box GF 2)
    - Cash, Alice (Box GF 2)
    - Chism, Michele (Box GF 2)
    - Coates, Ann (Box GF 2)
    - Crawford, Barbara (Box GF 2)
    - Crowe-Carraco, Carol (Box GF 2)
    - Davis, Glenetta (Box GF 2)
    - DeShazer, Mary (Box GF 2)
    - Donohue, Jean (Box GF 2)
    - Frederick, Sarah (Box GF 2)
    - Goldman, Pam (Box GF 2)
    - Gregory, Corinne (Box GF 2)
    - Griffin, Susan (Box GF 2)
    - Guyon, Marjorie (Box GF 2)
    - Hanger, Barbara (Box GF 2)
    - Hawkins, Mildred (Box GF 2)
    - Huard, Cynthia (Box GF 2)
    - Jensen, Julie (Box GF 2)
    - Kays, Jeanette (Box GF 2)
    - Kelly, Alex (Box GF 2)
    - Kennelly, Tamara (Box GF 2)
    - Kilb, Jenny (Box GF 2)
    - Kirstein, Janis (Box GF 2)
    - Kruse, Meriah (Box GF 2)
    - Kukla, Cynthia (Box GF 2)
    - Linderman, Laura (Box GF 2)
    - McIntosh, Peggy (Box GF 2)
    - Mitchell, Marie (Box GF 2)
    - Mitter, Sara (Box GF 2)
    - Morehead, Maureen (Box GF 2)
    - Mueller, Lavonne (Box GF 2)
    - Neumayer, Cora (Box GF 2)
    - Ostling, Kristin (Box GF 3)
    - Philpott, Linda (Box GF 3)
    - Powell, Irene (Box GF 3)
    - Reigler, Susan (Box GF 3)
    - Renick, Patricia (Box GF 3)
    - Robinson, Cathy (Box GF 3)
    - Sasso, Sandy (Box GF 3)
    - Shirley, Aleda (Box GF 3)
    - Sutton, Cathy (Box GF 3)
    - Thomas, Ursula (Box GF 3)
    - True, Vikki (Box GF 3)
    - Wood, Leslie (Box GF 3)
    - Zoe, Lucinda (Box GF 3)
  - 1987-1988 (Spring)
    - Appalshop (Box GF 3)
    - Artswatch (Box GF 3)
    - Community Coordinated Child Care (Box GF 3)
    - Education Arts, Inc. (Box GF 3)
    - Georgetown College (Box GF 3)
    - Kentucky Women's History Conference (Box GF 3)
    - Louisville Ballet (Box GF 3)
    - Mount St. Joseph Archives (Box GF 3)
    - Murray State University Visiting Artists (Box GF 3)
    - Planned Parenthood of Louisville (Box GF 3)
    - Shakespeare in the Fields (Box GF 3)
    - State of Mind Exhibit (Box GF 3)
    - University of Louisville Lectures (Box GF 3)
    - Virginia Center for the Creative Arts (Box GF 3)
  - 1987 Fall: Grants review papers (Box GF 3)
  - 1987-1988 (Fall):
    - Albrink, Nancy (Box GF 3)
    - Apple, Lisa (Box GF 3)
    - Arnillas, Liliana (Box GF 3)
    - Barnes, Linda (Box GF 3)
    - Block, Donna (Box GF 3)
    - Brock, Walter (Box GF 3)
    - Cassell, Nancy (Box GF 3)
    - Cobbs, Rae (Box GF 3)
    - Conway, Bethany (Box GF 3)
    - Cornett, Judy (Box GF 3)
    - Curry, Mary (Box GF 3)
    - Davis, Edith (Box GF 3)
    - DeCourcy, Lynne (Box GF 3)
    - Duke, Jeanette (Box GF 3)
    - Dunn, Millard (Box GF 3)
    - Erwin, Gaela (Box GF 3)
    - Glover, Sally (Box GF 3)
    - Goldstein, Joanna (Box GF 3)
    - Gordon, Lida (Box GF 3)
    - Graybeal, Patricia (Box GF 3)
    - Greenfield, Gretchen (Box GF 3)
    - Hamann, Marilyn (Box GF 3)
    - Hammett, Charlotte (Box GF 4)
    - Haragan, P. and Storey, A. (Box GF 4)
    - Hardesty, Sharon (Box GF 4)
    - Harman, Nancy (Box GF 4)
    - Hart, Lynda (Box GF 4)
    - Havens, Deborah (Box GF 4)
    - Hazelwood, Kimberly (Box GF 4)
    - Johnson, Fenton (Box GF 4)
    - Jordan, Joan (Box GF 4)
    - King, Lou (Box GF 4)
    - Kirchner, Erica (Box GF 4)
    - Knott, Caludia (Box GF 4)
    - Koger, Lisa (Box GF 4)
    - Kopacz, Paula (Box GF 4)
    - Lee, Shawn (Box GF 4)
    - Lindstorm, Anne (Box GF 4)
    - Maldonado, Mara (Box GF 4)
    - May, Kathy (Box GF 4)
    - McKinney, Irene (Box GF 4)
    - Metzmeier, B. and Rhodes, G. (Box GF 4)
    - Mitchell, Suzanne (Box GF 4)
    - Mock, R. and Clem D. (Box GF 4)
    - Naslund, Sena (Box GF 4)
    - Neal, Licia (Box GF 4)
    - Nixon, Rebecca (Box GF 4)
    - Norris, Lynne (Box GF 4)
    - Olmstead, Jane (Box GF 4)
    - Opengart, Bea (Box GF 4)
    - Penkalski, Janice (Box GF 4)
    - Phenix, Lucy (Box GF 4)
    - Richards, Veronica (Box GF 4)
    - Richardson, Josephine (Box GF 4)
    - Rodriguez, Janet (Box GF 4)
    - Sickles, Carol (Box GF 4)
    - Stewart, Deborah (Box GF 4)
    - Streepey, Janet (Box GF 4)
    - Wade, Barbara (Box GF 4)
    - Ward, Lucretia (Box GF 4)
    - Watson, Noelle (Box GF 4)
    - Weis, Ellen (Box GF 4)
    - Wilson, Melissa (Box GF 4)
    - Wood, McCrystle (Box GF 4)
    - Zaniello, Fran (Box GF 4)
    - Zimmerman, Marie (Box GF 4)
  - 1987-1988
    - Appalshop (Box GF 4)
    - Belles Lettres (Box GF 4)
    - Bunbury Repertory Theatre (Box GF 4)
    - Daedalus Productions (2 folders) (Box GF 4)
    - Kentucky State University (Box GF 4)
    - Roadside Theater (Box GF 4)
    - Speed Museum (Box GF 5)
    - University of Louisville Archives (Box GF 5)
    - Urban League of Lexington (Box GF 5)
    - Women Writers Conference (Box GF 5)
  - 1988: Grants review papers (Box GF 5)
  - 1988-1989
    - Baldyga, Julie (Box GF 5)
    - Binford, Anne (Box GF 5)
    - Blanton, Eileen (Box GF 5)
    - Christensen, Jean (Box GF 5)
    - Esselman, Mary (Box GF 5)
    - Foster, Catherine (Box GF 5)
    - Franklin, Angela (Box GF 5)
    - Furnish, Denise (Box GF 5)
    - Gaus, Donna (Box GF 5)
    - Gorham, Sarah (Box GF 5)
    - Hazelwood, Kimberly (Box GF 5)
    - Hickes, Robin (Box GF 5)
    - Irvin, Cass (Box GF 5)
    - Lyon, George Ella, et. al. (Box GF 5)
    - Mangine, Genevieve (Box GF 5)
    - Maxson, Richard (Box GF 5)
    - Miller, Zephra May (Box GF 5)
    - Mock, Robin and Deborah Clem (Box GF 5)
    - Morrison, Tracy (Box GF 5)
    - Morsey, Sara (Box GF 5)
    - Pierce, Constance (Box GF 5)
    - Price, Julia (Box GF 5)
    - Renick, Patricia (Box GF 5)
    - Rubio, Gwyn Ellen Hyman (Box GF 5)
    - Searfoss, Kristin (Box GF 5)
    - Shouse, Rebecca (Box GF 5)
    - Smith, Patty (Box GF 5)
    - Stone, Jo (Box GF 5)
    - Theriot, Nancy (Box GF 5)
    - Walker, Marsha (Box GF 5)
    - Wallace, Naomi (Box GF 5)
    - White, Pamela (Box GF 5)
    - Wood, Leslie (Box GF 5)
  - 1988-1989
    - Ars Femina (Box GF 5)
    - Artswatch (Box GF 5)
    - Filson Club (Box GF 5)
    - Louisville Visual Arts Association (Box GF 6)
    - Theatre on the Prowl (Box GF 6)
    - Youth Performing Arts School (Box GF 6)
  - 1990
    - Grants review papers (Box GF 6)
    - Appalshop (Box GF 6)
    - Arnillas, Liliana (Box GF 6)
    - Arnow, Jan (Box GF 6)
    - Artswatch (Box GF 6)
    - Blanton, Eileen (Box GF 6)
    - Cash, Jane (Box GF 6)
    - Darley, Claire (Box GF 6)
    - Dueber, Jeanne (Box GF 6)
    - Duncan, Laura (Box GF 6)
    - Dupree, Adora (Box GF 6)
    - England, Ana (Box GF 6)
    - Farnsley, Brenda (Box GF 6)
    - Farrell, Mary (Box GF 6)
    - Free, Phyllis and Ottzen, Susan (Box GF 6)
    - Grape, Carol (Box GF 6)
    - Kate and Company Productions (Box GF 6)
    - Kirchner, Erica (Box GF 6)
    - Kukla, Cynthia (Box GF 6)
    - LoPiccolo, Hather (Box GF 6)
    - Louisville Visual Art Association (Box GF 6)
    - Maddox, Laura (Box GF 6)
    - Montgomery, Patricia (Box GF 6)
    - Morris, Vanessa (Box GF 6)
    - Priest, Licia (Box GF 6)
    - Progressive Productions (Box GF 6)
    - Rauf, Barbara (Box GF 6)
    - The Road Company (Box GF 6)
    - Robinson, Catherine (Box GF 6)
    - Rodriguez, Susan (Box GF 6)
    - Sasso, Sandy (Box GF 6)
    - Seigel, Rebekka (Box GF 6)
    - Sisto, Penny (Box GF 6)
    - Skinner, Patricia (Box GF 6)
    - Spears, Karen (Box GF 6)
    - Sullivan, Celeste (Box GF 6)
    - Syncopated, Inc. (Box GF 6)
    - Taylor, Marilyn (Box GF 6)
    - Theater Workshop of Louisville (Box GF 6)
    - Volunteers of America, 2 folders (Box GF 7)
    - Walker, Melanie, D. Clem and R. Mock (Box GF 7)
    - Women in Theatre Festival (Box GF 7)
    - Women Writers Conference (Box GF 7)
    - Wood, Leslie (Box GF 7)
    - Yates, Dawn (Box GF 7)
    - Yer Girlfriend (Box GF 7)
  - 1991
    - Grants review papers (Box GF 7)
    - Alexander, Constance (Box GF 7)
    - Aprile, Dianne (Box GF 7)
    - Belles Lettres (Box GF 7)
    - Bivens, Yaa Floria (Box GF 7)
    - Boisseau, Michelle (Box GF 7)
    - Cebulska, Marcia (Box GF 7)
    - Clark, Cynthia (Box GF 7)
    - Cobbs, Rae (Box GF 7)
    - Colander, Valerie (Box GF 7)
    - Collins, Camilla (Box GF 7)
    - Darrell, Sherry (Box GF 7)
    - Davenport, Doris (Box GF 7)
    - Davis, Louise (Box GF 7)
    - Delgado, Pat (Box GF 7)
    - Finney, Nikky (Box GF 7)
    - Flodin, Lucinda (Box GF 7)
    - Gehringer, Martha (Box GF 7)
    - Gorham, Sarah (Box GF 7)
    - Hawkins, Mildred (Box GF 7)
    - Hazelwood, Kimerly (Box GF 7)
    - Holland, Suzanne (Box GF 7)
    - Irwin, Janet (Box GF 7)
    - Jones, Carridder (Box GF 7)
    - Jones, Marilyn (Box GF 7)
    - Jull, Sandra (Box GF 7)
    - Keelan, Claudia (Box GF 7)
    - Kilkelly, Ann (Box GF 7)
  - 1991 (Box GF 8)
    - Lehman, Rhea (Box GF 8)
    - Lutfiyya, M. and Whittenberger, K. (Box GF 8)
    - Maggard, Sally (Box GF 8)
    - McClanahan, Cia (Box GF 8)
    - McClellan, Eleanor (Box GF 8)
    - McElmurray, Karen (Box GF 8)
    - McMichael, Pam (Box GF 8)
    - Media Working Group (Box GF 8)
    - Morre, Michele (Box GF 8)
    - O'Connor, Kate (Box GF 8)
    - Osborn, Karen (Box GF 8)
    - R.A.P.E. Relief Center (2 folders) (Box GF 8)
    - Rosenman, Ellen (Box GF 8)
    - Skinner, Patricia (Box GF 8)
    - Source: Women Writers, 2 folders (Box GF 8)
    - Strange, Aralee (Box GF 8)
    - Taylor, Susan (Box GF 8)
    - Templeton, Alice (Box GF 8)
    - Weiner, Jennifer (Box GF 8)
    - Wolf, Geralyn (Box GF 8)
    - Women Writer's Conference (Box GF 8)
  - 1992
    - Grants review papers (Box GF 8)
    - Bacon, O'Leary (Box GF 8)
    - Barnette, Martha (Box GF 8)
    - Brooks, Nan (Box GF 8)
    - Clay, Angelique (Box GF 8)
    - Cunningham, Caren (Box GF 8)
  - 1992 (Box GF 9)
    - Darst, Stephanie (Box GF 9)
    - Dance Brigade (Box GF 9)
    - Edell, Therese (Box GF 9)
    - Einfalt, Linda (Box GF 9)
    - Erwin, Gaela (Box GF 9)
    - Fisher, Suzanne (Box GF 9)
    - Free, Phyllis (Box GF 9)
    - Good Name Productions (Box GF 9)
    - Graves, Jan (Box GF 9)
    - Higgins, Meg (Box GF 9)
    - Irwin, Kim (Box GF 9)
    - Kaufman, Barrie (Box GF 9)
    - Kleffman, Lois (Box GF 9)
    - Larke, Paula (Box GF 9)
    - Louisville Visual Art Association (Box GF 9)
    - Maier, Mary Anne and Chris Doerflinger, 2 folders (Box GF 9)
    - Morris, Vanessa (Box GF 9)
    - MUSE Cincinnati Women's Choir (Box GF 9)
    - New Harmony Gallery (Box GF 9)
    - Ogden, Joyce (Box GF 9)
    - Randall, Esther (Box GF 9)
    - Rowland, Wendy (Box GF 9)
    - Seeman, Rebecca (Box GF 9)
    - Speed Art Museum (Box GF 9)
    - Sydney, Sandra (Box GF 9)
    - Valois, Valerie (Box GF 9)
    - Virginia Center for the Creative Arts (Box GF 9)
    - Yaddo (Box GF 9)
    - Yer Girlfriend (Box GF 9)
  - 1993
    - Grants review papers (Box GF 9)
    - Alford-Haley, Carol (Box GF 9)
    - Anthony, Lillian (Box GF 9)
    - Artswatch (Box GF 9)
  - 1993 (Box GF 10)
    - Beasley, Gabrielle (Box GF 10)
    - Berry, George Ann (Box GF 10)
    - Bondurant, Jackie (Box GF 10)
    - Carnegie Center (Box GF 10)
    - French, Paula (Box GF 10)
    - Halpern, Susan (Box GF 10)
    - Hill, Heather (Box GF 10)
    - Hinton, Rebecca, 2 folders (Box GF 10)
    - Irwin, Cass (Box GF 10)
    - Johnson, Anne (Box GF 10)
    - Kern, Kathi (Box GF 10)
    - Lee, Diana (Box GF 10)
    - Maier, Mary Anne (Box GF 10)
    - Martin, Lou (Box GF 10)
    - Long, Kate (2 folders) (Box GF 10)
    - Marowitz, Jenny (Box GF 10)
    - Mary Anderson Center (Box GF 10)
    - Nichols, Krista (Box GF 10)
    - Opengart, Bea (Box GF 10)
    - Prager, Adele (Box GF 10)
    - Rysiewicz, Elaine (Box GF 10)
    - Sisters of Loretto (Box GF 10)
    - Snyder, Laura (Box GF 10)
    - University of Louisville Women's Center (Box GF 10)
    - Virginia Center for the Creative Arts (Box GF 10)
    - Women's Center, Volunteers of America (Box GF 10)
    - Waggener, Linda (Box GF 10)
    - Wagner, Stephanie (Box GF 10)
    - Wallace, Naomi (Box GF 10)
    - Werking, Kathy (Box GF 10)
    - Writer's Voice of the YMCA (Box GF 10)
- Accession (2001-0012), 1986-1998
  Conditions Governing Access note
  [Restricted: Patrons must sign an Acknowledgement of Legal Responsibilities and Privacy Rights form before using this collection.]
  - Contents of Box 1: (Box 1)
    [Audio and videocassettes found throughout box were removed and placed at the end of box 4.]
    - Outgoing correspondence (A-Z), 1994 (Box 1)
    - Board minutes, 1994 (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous and early decline grantee information (Box 1)
    - List and description of all grant applications received, 1994 (Box 1)
    - Grant applications for 1994 (Box 1)
    - Financial information, 1986-1992 (Box 1)
    - Approved grants, including evaluation forms and filed by grantee name, A-F, 1994 (Box 1)
  - Contents of Box 2: (Box 2)
    Audio and videocassettes found throughout box were removed and placed at the end of box 4.
    - Approved grants, including evaluation forms and filed by grantee name, F-W, 1994 (Box 2)
  - Contents of Box 3: (Box 3)
    - Approved grants, including evaluation forms and filed by grantee name, Y-Z, 1994 (Box 3)
    - The American Voice (TAV) information files, volumes 32-45, 1993-1998 (Box 3)
  - Contents of Box 4: (Box 4)
    - TAV volume 4, 1999 (Box 4)
    - TAV information files, volumes 46-49 (Box 4)
    - TAV correspondence (UK contract), 1998 (Box 4)
    - TAV correspondence (UK anthology: letters), 1998 (Box 4)
    - Correspondence, Maria Williams, 1998 (Box 4)
    - Sallie Bingham, preservation newspaper article, 1999 (Box 4)
    - Sallie Bingham, writings, reviews, etc., 1999 (Box 4)
    - Audio-visual material removed from box 1 (Box 4)
- Accession (2007-0126), 1986-2000, 5 boxes
  Addition consists primarily of files documenting the organization's grant program, and also includes project files, files related to the feminist literary journal The American Voice, publications, and files from Hopscotch House.
  - Correspondence with Sallie Bingham, 1992-1993 (Box (Acc. 07/126) 1)
  - The American Voice materials, 25 folders (Box (Acc. 07/126) 1)
    Layout, correspondence, fundraising, advertising, galleys, subscriptions, etc.
  - Julia Driskell, photographic exhibit from the International Women's Conference, Kenya, 1985 (Box (Acc. 07/126) 2)
  - Grant files, 1995 (Box (Acc. 07/126) 2)
  - Grant files, 1996 (Box (Acc. 07/126) 2)
  - Grant files, 1997 (Box (Acc. 07/126) 3)
  - Grant files, 1998 (Box (Acc. 07/126) 3)
  - Grant files, 1999 (Box (Acc. 07/126) 4)
  - Grant files, A-N, 2000 (Box (Acc. 07/126) 4)
  - Grant files, P-Z, 2000 (Box (Acc. 07/126) 5)
  - Board meetings, 1994-1996 (Box (Acc. 07/126) 5)
  - Printed materials
    - Grant Guidelines: Art Meets Activism, 2004-2006 (Box (Acc. 07/126) 5)
    - Grant Guidelines: Artist Enrichment, 2003-2006 (Box (Acc. 07/126) 5)
    - Special Initiative on Women, Art, and Change, 2000 (Box (Acc. 07/126) 5)
    - KFW Update, 2002-2006 (Box (Acc. 07/126) 5)
    - KFW Annual Report, 1988-2002 (Box (Acc. 07/126) 5)
    - KFW Newsletter, 1996-2000 (Box (Acc. 07/126) 5)
    - KFW Day Invitation, 2003-2006 (Box (Acc. 07/126) 5)
    - KFW Season's Greetings (Box (Acc. 07/126) 5)
    - Women's History Month Cards, 2004-2007 (Box (Acc. 07/126) 5)
    - KFW Brochure (Box (Acc. 07/126) 5)
  - Hopscotch House files
    - Hopscotch House history, 1988-2000 and undated (Box (Acc. 07/126) 5)
    - Hopscotch House manager, 1989-1999 and undated (Box (Acc. 07/126) 5)
    - Hopscotch House reports, 1997-2000 (Box (Acc. 07/126) 5)
    - Program information and fliers (Box (Acc. 07/126) 5)
    - Guest appraisals (Box (Acc. 07/126) 5)
    - Ann Stewart Anderson (Box (Acc. 07/126) 5)
    - Sallie Bingham (Box (Acc. 07/126) 5)
    - Slides (approximately 200), taken by Kristen Martin, 1990 (Box (Acc. 07/126) 5)
- Accession (2014-0152), 1997-2012; 19 boxes
  Scope and Contents
  Addition includes grant administration files, board records, and records of the retiring director Judi Jennings.
- Accession (2018-0026), (2018-0027), 2000-2017
  Conditions Governing Access
  A/V materials requre reformatting before use
  Arrangement
  Materials organized in the order in which they were received.
  Electronic records in this collection have been migrated to a library server and digital use copies can only be accessed onsite in the Rubenstein Library Reading Room. To request access, please contact a reference archivist before coming to use these records.
  - Artist Enrichment funded grants, 2009-2015 (Box 1-4)
  - Special Grant 2015: 30th Anniversary funded grants (Box 4)
  - Special Grant 2016: Radical, Timely and Urgent funded grants (Box 4)
  - Art Meets Activism funded grants, 2009-2016 (Box 5-7)
  - Final Reports, 2000-2008 (Box 8-9)
  - Annual reports, 2014-2017 (Box 10)
  - Board orientation and new policies, 2016 (Box 10)
  - Memo to board for grants, 2014-2016 (Box 10)
  - Collaborations, 2014-2017 (Box 10)
  - Sallie Bingham emails, 2014-2017 (Box 10)
  - Media mentions and awards, 2014-2017 (Box 10)
  - New initiatives, 2014-2017 (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, 2014-2017 (Box 10)
  - Videos, 2014-2017 (Box 10)
  - Summer Residency Program, 2005-2016 (Box 10)
    General
    Includes forms and procedures and one file per accepted artist including application, evaluation, and acceptance letter
  - Sallie Bingham video oral history, 2015-2017 (Digital-materials RL00773-SET-0001)
    One edited video file as well as one unedited video file clip (.mov format), 124 gigabytes.
    Collection contains electronic records that must be requested and accessed in our reading room. Contact Research Services with questions.
  - Ann Stewart Anderson video oral history, 2016-2017 (Digital-materials RL00773-SET-0002)
    One edited video file as well as 9 unedited video file clips (.mov format), 29.6 gigabytes.
  - Elmer Lucille Allen video oral history, 2016-2017 (Digital-materials RL00773-SET-0003)
    One edited video file as well as five unedited video file clips (.mov format), 13.6 gigabytes.